A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor E. Lee Trinkle, 1919-1929 [bulk 1922-1926]
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor E. Lee Trinkle, 1919-1929 [bulk 1922-1926]
The Library of Virginia
21567b
38.65 cu. ft. (103 boxes)
Trinkle, E. Lee, Records of Virginia Governor
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Office of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, 18 May 1939.
Biographical Information
Governor E. Lee Trinkle was born
Scope and Content
Governor E. Lee Trinkle Executive Papers, 1919-1929 [bulk 1922-1926], are organized into two series. Series have been designated for Subject Files and Extraditions and Pardons.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Subject Files, 1919-1929 [bulk 1922-1926]
Series II. Extraditions, Pardons, and Prison Affairs, 1922-1926
Contents List
- Series I: Subject files, 1919-1929 [bulk 1922-1926]., Extent: 27.3 cu. ft. (78 boxes). (Box Boxes 1-78)
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  - A, 1922. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A, 1923. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A, 1924. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - A, 1925. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - A, 1926. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Accountancy, State Board of, 1922-1925. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Accountant, State, Annual report, 1922. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Accountant, State, Annual report, 1923. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ackerly Case (Orange County, Va.), 1921-1922. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Addresses, 1922. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Addresses, Inaugural (material for), 1922-1923. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Adjutant General, 1922-1923. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Adjutant General, 1924-1925. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Advertising Club Conference, 1923. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Agricultural Advisory Committee, 1923. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Agriculture, Commissioner of, 1923-1925. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Agriculture and Immigration, State Board of, 1922-1925. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Alcoholism, World League Against, 1922. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Alexandria Party, 1923. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Aliens, Deportation of, 1922. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - American Academy of Political and Social Science, 1922-1925. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - American Association for labor legislation, 1923-1924. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - American Child Hygiene Association Convention, 1922. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - American Legion, 1922-1925. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - American Mining Congress, 1922-1923. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - American Prison Association, 1923-1926. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - American Public Health Association, 1924-1925. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Anti-Narcotic Conference, 1923. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Anti-Salon League Jubilee, 1924-1925. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Appointments (Delegates), 1922-1923. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Appointments (not requiring confirmation), 1919-1922. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Appointments (not requiring confirmation), 1923-1926. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Appointments (requiring confirmation), 1922-1926. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Art Commission, 1922-1925. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Atlantic Deeper Waterways Association, 1922. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Atlantic Deeper Waterways Association, 1923. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Atlantic Deeper Waterways Association, 1924-1925. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Attention, Governor's, 1923-1926. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Attorney General of Virginia, 1922-1927. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Auditing Committee, Annual Reports, 1922-1924. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1922-1925. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Auditor, Second, 1922-1923. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - B, 1922 February-July. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - B, 1922 August-December. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - B, 1923 January-May. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - B, 1923 June-December. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - B, 1924 January-May. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - B, 1924 June-December. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - B, 1925 January-June. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - B, 1925 July-1926 January. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Better Home Week, 1922-1923. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Bills, 1922-1925. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Blue Ridge Sanatorium, 1925. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Board of Barbers, 1924. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Bonds, 1922-1923 March 6. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Bonds, 1923 March 7-1924 December. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Boy Scouts, 1922-1924. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Brazilian Internation Centennial, 1922-1923. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Budget Advisory Commission, 1922-1925. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Budget Appropriations, 1922-1923. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Budget Appropriations, 1924-1925. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Budget Appropriation Requests, 1923. (Box 6, Folder 12-13)
  - Budget Director, 1924. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Budget Director, Col. Le Roy Hodges, 1921-1922. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Byrd, Harry, 1922-1923. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Byrd, Harry, 1924-1925. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - C, 1922. (Box 7, Folder 5-8)
  - C, 1923. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - C, 1923. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - C, 1924. (Box 8, Folder 2-4)
  - C, 1925. (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
  - Censorship Board, 1922 March. (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
  - Censors, State Board of, 1922-1923. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Censors, State Board of, 1924-1925. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Censors, State Board of, Reports, 1922-1924. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Child Labor Conference, 1923-1925. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Citizenship Conference, 1923. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Coal Administrator, 1922. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Coal Commission, 1923. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Coal Conference, Governor Pinchot (Pa.), 1923. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Coal contracts, 1922. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Coastal Highway Association, 1924. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - F.H. Combs, 1924-1925. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Commendatory letters, 1922. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Commendatory letters, 1923 January-June. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Commendatory letters, 1923 July-December. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Commendatory letters, 1924. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Commendatory letters, 1925-1926. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Commonwealth's Attorney, 1922-1923. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Commonwealth's Attorney, 1924. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Commonwealth's Attorney, 1925-1926. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Community Life Campaign, 1922. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Confederate Reunions, 1923-1924. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Congratulatory letters and telegrams, 1922. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Cooperative Education Association of Virginia, 1922-1923. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Contributions, Applications, 1922. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Contributions, Requests, 1922. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Contributions, Requests, 1923. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Contributions, Requests, 1923-1924. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Contributions, Requests, 1924-1926. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Cotton Tax Recovery Association, 1922. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Crenshaw, W.D., Lease, 1923. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - D, 1922. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - D, 1923. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - D, 1924. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - D, 1925. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - D, 1926. (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
  - D, Miscellaneous, 1922-1926. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Dairy Congress, 1923. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Dairy and Food Commissioners, 1923. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Dairy and Food Commissioners, 1924-1925. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Dairy and Food Commissioners, Commission candidates, T.C. Commins, 1923. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Dairy and Food Commissioners, Commission candidates, D.A. Kinsey, 1923. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Dairy and Food Commissioners, Commission candidates, A.B. Thornhill, 1923-1924. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Dairy, Food, and Drug Association, 1923. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Deaf and Blind Board, 1923-1924. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Deaf and Blind School (Staunton, Va.), Commission for separation of, 1922-1923. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - C.F. Deane (Clerk, Nottoway County, Va.), 1922. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Commissioners of Deeds, 1922-1926. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Defense Day Committee, 1924. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Dental Examiners, State Board of, 1922-1924. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Drainage Conference, 1922. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - E, 1922-1923. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - E, 1924. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - E, 1925. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Education, 1922-1925. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Election, Writ of, 1925. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Embalming, State Board of, 1922-1925. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Engineers, Architects and Land Surveyors, State Board of, 1922-1925. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Escheators, 1922-1925. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Examiners of Records, 1922-1925. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Ex-Service men, 1922. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - F, 1922. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - F, 1923. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - F, 1924. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - F, 1925. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Financial Advertisers' Association, 1924. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Fire Prevention, 1922-1924. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Fisheries, Commissioner of, 1921-1922. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Fisheries, Commissioner of, 1923. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Fisheries, Commissioner of, 1924. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Fisheries, Commissioner of, 1925. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Fisheries, Commissioner of, Applicants, C.F. Beverley, 1921. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Fisheries, Commissioner of, Applicants, V.L. Henderson, 1921. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Fisheries, Commissioner of, Applicants, J.P.M. Joyce, 1921. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Fisheries, Commissioner of, Applicants, Otto Law, 1923. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Fisheries, Commissioner of, Applicants, W. McDonald Lee, 1921. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Fisheries, Commissioner of, Applicants, S.W. Matthews, 1923. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Fisheries, Commissioner of, Applicants, A.F. Morrisett, 1921. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Fisheries, Commissioner of, Applicants, Spencer F. Rogers, 1923. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Florida, 1925. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Fontainebleau School of Music for Americans, 1921-1922. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - "Fool file", 1922-1924. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Forest, Forest warden, 1922. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Forest, Forest warden, 1923. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Forest, Forest warden, 1924. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Forest, Forest warden, 1925-1926. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Forester, State, 1922-1923. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Forester, State, 1924. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Forester, State, 1925. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Forestry, Southern Congress of, 1922-1925. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - "For-Get-Me-Not," 1922-1924. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - G, 1922. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - G, 1923. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - G, 1924. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - G, 1925. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, 1922-1923. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, 1924. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, 1925 January-August. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, 1925 September-1926 January. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Garrett trial (Cumberland County, Va.), 1923-1924. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Gasoline Inspection Bill, 1921-1923. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Gasoline prices, 1923. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Gasoline tax, 1924-1925. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - General Assembly, Addresses, 1923-1925. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - General Assembly, Bills, approved by Governor, 1923. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - General Assembly, Bills not approved, 1922-1923. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - General Assembly, Bills complaints, 1922-1923. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - General Assembly, Bills complaints, 1924. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - General Assembly, Bills to be presented, 1923-1924. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - General Assembly, Bills, Requests in connection with, 1922-1923. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - General Assembly, Bills signed, Inquiries as to, 1924. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - General Assembly, Extra session, 1922 March-June. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - General Assembly, Extra session, 1922 March-July. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - General Assembly, Extra session, 1922 April-July. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - General Assembly, Extra session, 1922 September-November. (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
  - General Assembly, Extra session, 1922 September-December. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - General Assembly, Extra session, 1922 October-November. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - General Assembly, Extra session, 1922 November-December. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - General Assembly, Extra session, 1922 December. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - General Assembly, Extra session, 1922 October-1923 January. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - General Assembly, Extra session, 1925. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - General Assembly, Members, 1922-1923. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - General Assembly, Members, 1924-1925. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - General Assembly, Messages of Governor to, 1922-1924. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - General Assembly, Resignations, 1922-1923. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Geological Commission, 1922-1925. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Gold Star Highway Commission, 1925. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Automobile titles, 1925. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey, 1922-1925. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Conference, 1922-1924. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Governor's Conference, 1925 January-June. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Governor's Conference, 1925 July-1926 January. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Governor's expense account, 1923-1924. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Governor's Mansion, 1922. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Mansion, Decorative examples, nd. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Office, Pay roll, 1925-1928. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Governor's Office Staff, 1922-1925. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Grounds and Buildings, Superintendent of, 1922-1925. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - H, 1922. (Box 21, Folder 6-7)
  - H, 1923. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - H, 1923-1924. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - H, 1923-1924. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - H, 1924-1925. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - H, 1925. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Hampton Institute, 1925. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Hampton Roads Port Commission, 1922. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Hampton Roads Port Commission, 1923. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Hampton Roads Port Commission, Applications, 1922. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Harding Memorial Association, 1923. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Highways, 1922. (Box 22, Folder 9-10)
  - Highways, 1922. (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - Highways, 1922-1923. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Highways, 1923-1924. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Highway, Association of Highways of America Convention, 1922. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Highways, Bond issue, 1922. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Highways, Bond Issue, 1922. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Highway Commission, Annual reports, 1922-1926. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Highway Commission, 1922-1923. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Highway Commission, 1924. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Highway Commission, 1924-1925. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Highway Commission, 1925-1926. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Highway Commission, Applications, Various, 1922. (Box 24, Folder 3-4)
  - Highway Commission, Applications (Anderson, Jesse), 1922. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Highway Commission, Applications (B - D), 1922. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Highway Commission, Applications (G - H), 1922. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Highway Commission, Applications (Hardaway, Horace), 1922. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Highway Commission, Applications (Lane, Henry L.), 1922. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Highway Commission, Applications (J - S), 1922. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Highway Commission, Applications (Lewis, J. Marshall), 1922. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Highway Commission, Applications (Massie, Wade H.), 1922. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Highway Commission, Applications (Sanders, R.K.), 1922. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Highway Commission, Applications (Snell, Olney E.), 1922. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Highway Commission, Applications (Sproul, Hugh B.), 1922. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Highway Commission, Applications (Truxton, Major I. Walke), 1922. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Highway Commission, Applications (Truxton, Major I. Walke), Successor after resignation, 1925. (Box 25, Folder 8-9)
  - Highway Commission, Applications (Wallinger, C.H.), 1922. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Highway Commission, Applications (Weaver, R.S.), 1922. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Highway Commissioner, George P. Coleman, 1922. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Highways Department, Applications, 1922-1925. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Highways Department, Building, 1923. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Highways, Routes, 1922. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Highways, Routes, 1923. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Highways, Routes, 1923-1924. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Highways, Routes, 1924. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Highways, Routes, 1924-1925. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Highways, Routes, 1925-1926. (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Highways, Statements, 1923. (Box 27, Folder 1-3)
  - Highways, Statements, 1924-1926. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Highways, Unsorted, 1924-1925. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Historical Spots, Board to Mark, 1922-1925. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Hodges, Le Roy, 1922-1924. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Holidays, State, 1922. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Hospitals, Central State (Petersburg, Va.), 1922-1925. (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Hospitals, Eastern State (Williamsburg, Va.), 1922-1925. (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Hospitals, Southwestern State (Marion, Va.), 1922-1925. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Hospitals, State Colony for Epileptics and Feeble-Minded (Lynchburg, Va.), 1922-1925. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Hospitals, Western State (Staunton, Va.), 1922-1926. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Hospitals, Commissioner of State, 1922-1925. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Houdoun, Statue of George Washington, 1924. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - I, 1922-1924. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Illiteracy Conference, 1922-1923. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Illiteracy Conference, 1923-1924. (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Indian Schools, 1924. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Industrial Commission, 1921. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Industrial Commission, 1922 January-May. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Industrial Commission, 1922 June-December. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Industrial Commission, 1923. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Industrial Commission, 1924. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Industrial Commission, 1925-1926. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Insurance Bureau, 1922-1925. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - International Farmers Congress, 1923. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - International Trade Commission, 1922. (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - International Trade Exhibition, 1925. (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1922-1925. (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Invitations, 1922 January-February. (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Invitations, 1922 March. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, 1922 April. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, 1922 May 1-15. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, 1922 May 16-31. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, 1922 June. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, 1922 July. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Invitations, 1922 August. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Invitations, 1922 September. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Invitations, 1922 September. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, 1922 October. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, 1922 November. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, 1922 December. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, 1923 January-February. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, 1923 February-March. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Invitations, 1923 April. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Invitations, 1923 April-May. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, 1923 May. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, 1923 May-June. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, 1923 July. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, 1923 August. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, 1923 September. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Invitations, 1923 October. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Invitations, 1923 November. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, 1923 December. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, 1924 January. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, 1924 February-March. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, 1924 April. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, 1924 April-May. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Invitations, 1924 May. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Invitations, 1924 June. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Invitations, 1924 July. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, 1924 August. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, 1924 September - October. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, 1924 November. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, 1924 December. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, 1925 January. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Invitations, 1925 February. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Invitations, 1925 March. (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Invitations, 1925 April. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, 1925 May. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, 1925 June. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, 1925 July. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, 1925 August. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, 1925 September. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Invitations, 1925 October. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Invitations, 1925 November - December. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, 1926 January. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, Join clubs and orders, 1922-1923. (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, Lists, 1922. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - J, 1922-1923. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - J, 1923. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - J, 1924-1925. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Judges, Designation of, 1922. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Judges, Designation of, 1922. (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Judges, Designation of, 1923. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Judges, Designation of, 1923. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Judges, Designation of, 1923-1924. (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Judges, Designation of, 1924. (Box 37, Folder 4-6)
  - Judges, Designation of, 1925. (Box 38, Folder 1-4)
  - Judges, Designation of, 1925-1926. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Judges, Appointment of, 1922-1925. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Judgeships, 4th Judicial District, Endorsements of Edwin P. Cox, 1924. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Judgeships, 4th Judicial District, Endorsements of Allen Epes, 1924. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Judgeships, 4th Judicial District, Endorsements of T. Freeman Epes, 1924. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Judgeships, 4th Judicial District, Endorsements of J.G. Jefferson, 1924. (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Judgeships, 5th Judicial District, Endorsements of A.B. Dickinson, 1924. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Judgeships, 5th Judicial District, Endorsements of Robert F. Hutcheson, 1924. (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Judgeships, 15th Judicial District, Endorsements of various, 1924. (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
  - Judgeships, Virginia Supreme Court of Appeals, Endorsements of Thomas J. Barham, 1925. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Judgeships, Virginia Supreme Court of Appeals, Endorsements of R.H.L. Chichester, 1925. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Judgeships, Virginia Supreme Court of Appeals, Endorsements of Joseph W. Chinn, 1925. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Judgeships, Virginia Supreme Court of Appeals, Endorsements of George Latham Fletcher, 1925. (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Judgeships, Virginia Supreme Court of Appeals, Endorsements of Thomas R. Keith, 1925. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Judgeships, Virginia Supreme Court of Appeals, Endorsements of various, 1925. (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Judgeships, Endorsements of various positions, 1921-1926. (Box 40, Folder 9-10)
  - K, 1922. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - K, 1923. (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - K, 1924-1925. (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Kellogg, Frank B., 1925. (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - King and Queen County Lynching, 1923. (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - L, 1922. (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - L, 1923. (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - L, 1924. (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - L, 1925. (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Labor, Commissioner of, 1921-1922. (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Labor Commission, 1922. (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Labor Commission, 1923. (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Labor Commission, 1924-1925. (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Land Grants, 1922-1925. (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - "Law and Order" Sunday, 1925. (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Law Enforcement, 1922-1925. (Box 42, Folder 4-6)
  - League of Women Voters, 1922-1926. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Leases, 1922. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Lee Highway, 1922-1924. (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Lee, McDonald, Investigation, 1924. (Box 42, Folder 10-11)
  - Legislation, New, 1921-1924. (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Legislation, Uniformity, 1922-1924. (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Legislation, US, 1923-1925. (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Legislative complaints, 1923. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Legislative reference, 1924. (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Legislative suggestions, 1922-1924. (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Lime Grinding Board, 1922-1923. (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Lincoln Memorial, 1922. (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Living Hall of Fame, 1922. (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Lists, 1922-1925. (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Mc, 1922-1923. (Box 43, Folder 11)